Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV. Youth Section/Young Democratic Socialists of America, 1972-2012; 22.6 Linear Feet in 42 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 oversized flat box, 2 folders in 1 shared box; 1 VHS; 4 audiocassettes; 5 Hi8; 2 sound tape reels; 54.82 Gigabytes in 365 computer files
  - Events and Programs -- University in Society Project, 1985-1988 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Events and Programs -- South Africa Initiatives, 1985-1990 (Box 75, Folder 2, Box Shared Tamiment 174, Folder 18)
  - Events and Programs -- Reproductive Rights Initiatives, 1985-1996 (Box 75, Folder 3-5)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1985-1990 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Events and Programs -- Nicaraguan Student Tours and Student Exchange, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- Summer Leadership Schools, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- National Mobilization for Justice and Peace in Central America and Southern Africa, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- Unidentified March -- New York City, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- Poverty Project, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Events and Programs -- National Rainbow Student and Youth Convention and Jackson Campaign, 1987-1988 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Events and Programs -- Core Curriculum/Anti-Racist Initiatives, 1987-1990 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Events and Programs -- National Student Convention '88, February 1988 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- Democratic National Convention, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Events and Programs -- Young Women's Conference Committee, 1988-1990 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Events and Programs -- Billy Bragg and Pete Seeger Concerts, 1988-1990 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Events and Programs -- Campus Labor Institutes, 1988-1994 (Box 78, Folder 1-2)
  - Events and Programs -- Student Solidarity Vigil for Students in China, June 1989 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- Trip to Jamaica with People's National Party Youth Organization, March 1990 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- National Student and Youth Campaign for Peace in the Middle East, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- Student Environmental Action Coalition Conference, 1991-1995 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 1991-1996 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Events and Programs -- Youth Delegation to Mexico and Fair Trade Project, 1992-1993 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Events and Programs -- Lollapalooza Forum Tent, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- Solidarity Summer, 1994
    - Correspondence, Flyers, Schedules, and Agendas (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_56
  - Events and Programs -- Summer Study Group, 1994; TW_TAM_105_ER_57
  - Events and Programs -- University Conversion Project, 1994; TW_TAM_105_ER_58
  - Events and Programs -- Campus Organizing Retreat, March 1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- March 29 Day of Action, March 1995; TW_TAM_105_ER_59
  - Events and Programs -- Stop the Campus Gag Rule, July 1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- Labor Notes Conference, 1995; TW_TAM_105_ER_60
  - Events and Programs -- Summer Institutes, 1995-2001 (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
  - Events and Programs -- Winter Retreat, February 1996 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Events and Programs -- "Our City…Our Future: A People's Hearing on Youth and Economic Insecurity" -- New York, March 1996
    - Correspondence, Brochures, and Programs (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0117)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0118)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0119)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0120)
    - Video Recording (Box 155, Hi8 105.0121)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_61
  - Events and Programs -- Days of Action in Defense of Immigrant Rights and Affirmative Action, March-April 1996 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Events and Programs -- Union Summer, 1996-1997 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Events and Programs -- "Making Trouble: Building a Radical Youth Movement" -- Berkeley, April 1998; TW_TAM_105_ER_62
  - Events and Programs -- The Stop Sweatshop Campaign, 1999; TW_TAM_105_ER_63
  - Events and Programs -- Teach-Ins and Workshops, 2000-2005; TW_TAM_105_ER_66
  - Events and Programs -- General, 2000-2012
    - Flyers, Postcards, and Correspondence, 2000-2012 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Posters, 2003-2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_68
    - Unidentified Events -- Electronic Records, circa 2007-2009; TW_TAM_105_ER_74
  - Events and Programs -- International Forum on Globalization Youth Meeting, January 2001; TW_TAM_105_ER_64
  - Events and Programs -- Recruitment Campaign, 2001; TW_TAM_105_ER_65
  - Events and Programs -- Guerilla Sex Education Project Proposal, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_67
  - Events and Programs -- Active Arts Youth Council Proposal, 2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_69
  - Events and Programs -- Books Not Bombs, 2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_70
  - Events and Programs -- Joseph Schwartz -- "Socialism: Now More Than Ever", March 2006; TW_TAM_105_ER_232
  - Events and Programs -- International Union of Socialist Youth 2006 World Festival, July 2006; TW_TAM_105_ER_71
  - Events and Programs -- United States Social Forum, June 2007
    - Correspondence, Program, and Agendas, June 2007 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - "As Radical as Reality", June 2007; TW_TAM_105_ER_229
  - Events and Programs -- National Youth and Student Peace Coalition, 2007 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Events and Programs -- Students for a Democratic Society Conventions, 2007-2008 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Events and Programs -- "Justice Beyond Borders", circa 2007-2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_72
  - Events and Programs -- Marches/Protests, circa 2007-2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_73
  - Events and Programs -- Tent State University at the Democratic National Convention, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Events and Programs -- Summer School, 2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_75 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Events and Programs -- "2013 Isn't Soon Enough", circa 2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_76
  - Events and Programs -- Racial Justice Panel, circa 2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_78
  - Events and Programs -- "Shake It to the Left" Party, circa 2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_77
  - Events and Programs -- Hand Painted Banner for Rallies and Marches (Box 153)
  - Events and Programs -- General, 2011-2016 (Box 341, Folder 12)
  - Membership -- Brochures, circa 1979-1999 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Membership -- Surveys, circa 1995 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Membership -- Surveys, 1999-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_79
  - Membership -- New Member Packet, 2008-2009 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1976-1979 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1980 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 11, Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 5-6)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1986 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 2-3)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 4-5)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 1-2)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1993-1994 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 1995-1996 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 2000 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Membership -- Key List Mailings, 2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_80
  - Fundraising -- Appeals, 1994-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_81
  - Fundraising -- Proposals and Initiatives, 1981-1997 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Socialist Organizing Weekend, 2014 (Box 341, Folder 15)
  - YDS Feminist Reader, 2003 (Box 341, Folder 18)
  - YDS Reader, 2009 (Box 341, Folder 19)
  - Young Democratic Socialists of America Website, circa 2006-2010; TW_TAM_105_ER_82
- Series V. Staff and Administrative Materials, 1946-2006; 17.54 Linear Feet in 39 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, and 1 flat box; 6 audiocassettes; 4.22 Megabytes in 158 computer files
  Arranged first by individual staff member, chronologically by years of service, then alphabetically (with the exception of "General Correspondence") by topic.
  This series mostly consists of materials created by the staff at the national office. These materials reflect the day-to-day administrative tasks, as well as the national oversight of numerous chapters, performed by the staff members of DSOC, NAM, and DSA. Materials include general financial records (mostly budgets), internal memos, staff meeting minutes, and directors' correspondence and reports. Additionally, there is biographical material, writing (both published and unpublished), and publicity on and by Michael Harrington. Items include correspondence between Harrington and publishers; copies of his CV; drafts, publications, and notes written by Harrington; reviews of his writing; clippings of his appearances; and interviews with him. Writing, publicity, and biographical information on other prominent staff members, including Carl Shier, a founding member of DSOC; Jack Clark, the first national organizer of DSOC; Harry Boyte, a leading figure of NAM; and Barbara Ehrenreich, a co-chair of DSA, are included. There is general correspondence with members about dues and registration; chapter leaders about the number of delegates apportioned to the national convention; other organizations on co-sponsoring events; and individuals about conference and other event participation.
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 85, Folder 4-5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 86, Folder 1-3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 4-5, Box 87, Folder 1-2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 3-5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 1-4, Box 89, Folder 1-2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 3-4, Box 90, Folder 1-4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 5, Box 91, Folder 1-4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1982 (Box 91, Folder 5, Box 92, Folder 1-3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 4-6)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1984 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 2-3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1986 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 6, Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Correspondence, undated (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Awards and Honors, 1973-1989 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Business Cards, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Civil Action Against United States Naval Officers, 1975 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Curricula Vitae and Biographies, 1946-1988 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Date Books, 1964-1979 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Date Books, 1984-1985 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Date Books, 1986-1989 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1973-1980 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1982-1983 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1985 (Box 96, Folder 3-4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1987 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Lectures and Other Engagements, 1988-1989 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Photographs and Drawings, 1974-1989 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Press and Publicity, 1970-1975 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Press and Publicity, 1976-1980 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Press and Publicity, 1981-1988 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Press and Publicity, 1988-1989, 1995
    - Flyers, Press Releases, and Clippings (Box 98, Folder 2-3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_91
  - Harrington, Michael -- Published Writing -- Royalties, Correspondence, and Permissions, 1972-1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Published Writing, 1973-1980 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Published Writing, 1980-1984 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Published Writing, 1985-1989 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- National Public Radio Commentary, 1985-1989 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing -- Speeches, Lectures, and Drafts, circa 1972-1976 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing -- Speeches, Lectures, and Drafts, circa 1976-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing -- Speeches, Lectures, and Drafts, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing -- Speeches, Lectures, and Drafts, 1981-1985 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Unpublished Writing -- Speeches, Lectures, and Drafts, 1985-1989 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Harrington, Michael -- Notes, circa 1974-1985 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Shier, Carl -- Correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Jack -- Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Jack -- Correspondence, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Jack -- Correspondence, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 5, Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Clark, Jack -- Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Clark, Jack -- Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Clark, Jack -- Curriculum Vitae and Publicity, 1975-1976 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Clark, Jack -- National Tour Logs and Evaluations, 1975 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Clark, Jack -- Reports and Writing, 1974-1978 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Boyte, Harry -- New American Movement -- Correspondence and Writing, 1974-1982 (Box 301, Folder 5)
  - Chapin, Jim -- Correspondence and Writing, 1978-1988 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Chapin, Jim -- Memorial, 2002; TW_TAM_105_ER_84
  - Ehrenreich, Barbara -- Biography and Writing, 1983-1990 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Charney, Alan -- Correspondence, 1993-1995
    - Letters and Emails (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_85
  - Other Staff Members -- Writing and Publicity, 1974-1985 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Budgets, 1974-2003
    - DSOC and DSA -- Paper Documents, 1974-1993 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - NAM -- Paper Documents, 1977-1982 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - Electronic Records, 1998-2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_83
  - Job Listings, 1987-1992 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Job Listings, 1998-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_92
  - Legal Issues, 1991-2006 (Box 104, Folder 5-6)
  - Office Calendars, circa 1976-1985 (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Office Calendar, 2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_93
  - Office Forms and Procedures, 1972-1998
    - NAM, 1972 (Box 301, Folder 7)
    - DSOC and DSA, 1979-1998 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Staff Goals, Functions, and Reports, 1980-1998
    - Memos and Correspondence (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_94
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Staff Meeting Minutes, Reports, and Notes, 1973-1980 (Box 301, Folder 8)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1972-May 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, June 1977-August 1978 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, September 1978-September 1979 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, October 1979-1981 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1982-1984 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1984 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1984-1989 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1991-1993 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 1995-1999
    - Paper Files (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_95
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 2000-2003; TW_TAM_105_ER_96
  - Staff Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Memos, 2012-2018 (Box 343, Folder 2)
  - Staff Photographs, circa 1982-1995 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Staff Retreat, January 1997
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0093)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0094)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0095)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0096)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0097)
    - Audio Recording (Box 155, Audiocassette 105.0098)
  - General Correspondence, 1969-1981
    - Pre-DSOC/DSOC, 1969-1971 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - NAM, 1971 (Box 301, Folder 9)
    - NAM, 1972 (Box 302, Folder 1-2)
    - DSOC, 1972-1974 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - NAM, 1973 (Box 302, Folder 3-4)
    - NAM, 1974 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - DSOC, 1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - NAM, 1975 (Box 302, Folder 6-7)
    - DSOC, 1976 (Box 108, Folder 3-6)
    - NAM, 1976 (Box 303, Folder 1-2)
    - DSOC, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 1-4)
    - NAM, 1977 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - DSOC, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 5, Box 110, Folder 1-4)
    - NAM, 1978 (Box 303, Folder 4-5)
    - DSOC, 1979 (Box 111, Folder 1-4, Box 112, Folder 1-2)
    - DSOC, circa 1979-1981 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - NAM, 1979-1982 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - DSOC, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 4-5, Box 113, Folder 1-4)
    - DSOC, 1981 (Box 114, Folder 1-4, Box 115, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1982 (Box 115, Folder 3-5, Box 116, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 3-5)
  - General Correspondence, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 6, Box 117, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 3-5, Box 118, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1986 (Box 118, Folder 3-6)
  - General Correspondence, 1987 (Box 119, Folder 1-2)
  - General Correspondence, 1988 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence, 1989 (Box 119, Folder 4-5)
  - General Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence, 1992-1994
    - Paper Files (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_86
  - General Correspondence, 1995
    - Paper Files (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_87
  - General Correspondence, 1996
    - Paper Files (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_88
  - General Correspondence, 1997-1999
    - Paper Files (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Electronic Records, TW_TAM_105_ER_89
  - General Correspondence, 2000-2004; TW_TAM_105_ER_90
  - Website, 1997; TW_TAM_105_ER_97
  - Small Firm Attraction and Retention Grant Program, 2009 (Box 342, Folder 27)
- Series VI. Conventions, 1971-2007; 12.33 Linear Feet in 23 manuscript boxes, 3 flat boxes, and 3 folders in 2 shared boxes; 25 audiocassettes; 2 Hi8; 18 VHS; 3.72 Gigabytes in 144 computer files
  This series contains materials related to DSA's National Convention, which is currently held every other year. The election of members of the National Political Committee (NPC), the highest decision-making body between conventions, occurs during each Convention. The significance of the National Convention is reflected in the various resolutions and political priorities discussed, passed, and/or tabled during the proceedings. Materials cover the first conventions of DSOC and NAM through conventions in the 2010s, and include programs, agendas, mailings to speakers, speeches, papers delivered, registration materials, facilities information, press packets, resolutions, and audiovisual recordings of speeches and conference sessions.
  Bibliography
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Thanksgiving/Program Conference -- Davenport, November 1971 (Box 304, Folder 1-4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Founding Convention, June 1972 (Box 121, Folder 1, Box Shared Tamiment 171, Folder 11, Box 305, Folder 1-2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Second Convention, July 1973 (Box 121, Folder 2, Box 305, Folder 3, Box 306, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Founding Convention, October 1973 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- "Socialist Perspectives in the Democratic Party", May 1974 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Third Convention, July 1974 (Box 121, Folder 5, Box 306, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Membership Conference and Socialist Weekend, September 1974 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Second National Convention, January 1975 (Box 121, Folder 7, Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- "The American Political Economy in Crisis", circa April 1975 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Socialist Weekend, May-June 1975 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, August 1975 (Box 306, Folder 3-4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Bay Area Educational Conference -- "Who Should Own California? Alternatives to Corporate Control", October 1975 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Convention, January-February 1976 (Box 122, Folder 5-6)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, August 1976 (Box 122, Folder 7, Box 307, Folder 1-2)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Third National Convention, February 1977 (Box 122, Folder 8, Box 123, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, August 1977 (Box 123, Folder 2, Box 307, Folder 3-4)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Unidentified Convention Schedule, circa 1977-1981 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Northeast Regional Convention, April 1978 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- National Convention, July 1978 (Box 123, Folder 5, Box 308, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Fourth National Convention, February 1979 (Box 123, Folder 6-7, Box 124, Folder 1)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, August 1979 (Box 124, Folder 2, Box 308)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Conference of the Industrial Heartland Region -- "Strategies for the 80s", circa June 1980 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, July 1980 (Box 124, Folder 4, Box 308, Folder 3)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) and New American Movement (NAM) -- "Urban Politics in the 80s: A Conference", March 1981 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee (DSOC) -- Fifth National Convention, May 1981 (Box 124, Folder 6-7, Box 125, Folder 1-2)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- Convention, July-August 1981 (Box 125, Folder 3, Box 308, Folder 4)
  - New American Movement (NAM) -- War and Imperialism Conference, undated (Box 125, Folder 4)